communitycash.com 2015-05-12

# CommunityCash : Privacy Policy

Community Cash respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. As an individual using our website, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy very carefully when using our websites or services or conducting business with us. By using our websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

**Information Collected**

Community Cash may collect from you both identifying and non-identifying personal information through our websites or other manner.

_Information provided by you._ Â Community Cash may require that you provide certain information to use the services on our site.Â  You may always decline to give any personal information requested by Community Cash, but without the presentation of such information, Community Cash may not be able to provide services to you.Â 

_Cookies_. When you visit MyCommunityCash.com, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our websites, to personalize your online experience, and to record information about your visit to our websites. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our websites, such as the web pages you visit, the links or advertisements you click, or the other actions you conduct while visiting MyCommunityCash.com if you have enabled cookies.

_IP Address._ MyCommunityCash.com automatically collects your IP address, access times, and the referring website address for identification purposes.

_Personal Information_.Â  This website does not collect, save or store any personal information from visitors that simply browse this website, unless you voluntarily and intentionally provide it to us. We do not collect personal information without your knowledge or consent.

_Embedded Advertisements._ Advertisements displayed on Community Cashâ€™s web sites may be delivered via an advertising management service. When you view a web page on our web site that contains advertising provided one of our advertising management services, the advertising service company may place a cookie on or retrieve a cookie from your computer if you have enabled cookies.

_User Communications._ Â  Users of MyCommunityCash.com may from time to time contact Community Cash with inquiries or requests.Â  Community Cash will retain these communications in order to process and respond to these inquiries and requests.

**Disclosure of Information**

Community Cash may disclose your information:Â  (1) in response to a subpoena, court order, or a request for cooperation from law enforcement agencies; (2) to defend against legal claims; (3) when we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activity, fraud or wrongdoing; (4) to protect the rights, property, and safety of our company, users, employees or others; (5) to enforce our website terms; (6) in the event of a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, merger, or consolidation; or (7) as otherwise required by law.

**_The previous paragraphs notwithstanding, Community Cash will not disclose your information, and uses all of the information collected solely for analytical purposes connected to the operation of the Site._**

**Protection of Your Information**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure.Â  Access to your personal information is restricted to Community Cashâ€™s employees, contractors, and agents, for whom the information is necessary to maintain and improve our services.Â 

Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm> for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

**Modification of this Privacy Policy**

Community Cash reserves the right to, and may from time to time, make changes to this privacy policy.

Additionally, if you have any concerns about security on CommunityCash.com, you can email us at info@CommunityCash.com with any questions.
